var quizArray = [
    {
        question: "1 + 2 = ?",
        options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        answer: 2
    },{
        question: "5 + 19 = ?",
        options: ["23", "24", "26", "29"],
        answer: 1
    },{
        question: "23 - 8 = ?",
        options: ["15", "16", "17", "18"],
        answer: 0
    },{
        question: "5 * 4 = ?",
        options: ["25", "20", "35", "30"],
        answer: 1
    },{
        question: "3 + 2 * 10 = ?",
        options: ["32", "30", "23", "50"],
        answer: 2
    },{
        question: "2 + 7 - 8 * 4 = ?",
        options: ["-21", "-23", "-25", "-27"],
        answer: 1
    },{
        question: "15 * 6 + 9 * 5 = ?",
        options: ["105", "175", "125", "135"],
        answer: 3
    },{
        question: "23 * (41 + 86) = ?",
        options: ["1221", "2121", "2921", "3121"],
        answer: 2
    },{
        question: "5.837 / 9 = ?",
        options: ["0.6486", "0.6372", "0.6392", "0.6436"],
        answer: 0
    },{
        question: "(914 - 298) * 6.14 = ?",
        options: ["3282.74", "3782.24", "3302.24", "3972.24"],
        answer: 1
    }
];